Finding Aid for the Alex North Motion Picture Music PASC-M.0017
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Go Man Go [United Artists, 1954]
  - North, Alex. [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score (128 leaves)] [Ozalid copy of piano I & II parts (26 leaves)] (Box 5, Folder 16-17)
    - Main Title, 13 [1-13] (Othertype 1 1)
    - Barnstorming, 10 [14-23] (Othertype 1 2)
    - Rejected, 8 [24-31] (Othertype 1 3)
    - Abe's Philosophy, 4 [32-35] (Othertype 2 1)
    - Newspaper items, 6 [36-41] (Othertype 2 2)
    - In transit, 3 [42-44] (Othertype 3 1)
    - Haine's dribble, 6 [45-50] (Othertype 3 2)
    - Sylvia, 5 [51-55] (Othertype 4 1)
    - Abe's dream, 7 [56-62] (Othertype 4 2)
    - Defeat montage, 7 [63-69] (Othertype 4 3)
    - Comedy, 6 [70-75] (Othertype 5 1)
    - Romance, 14[76-89] (Othertype 7 1)
    - Willouby, 11 [90-100] (Othertype 8 1)
    - Tournament, 5 [101-105] (Othertype 8 2)
    - Madison Sq trailing, 1 [106] (Othertype 8 3)
    - Madison Square final, 22 [107-128] (Othertype 9 1)
    - Main title, (3 folded) 5 (8 pp) [129-133] (Othertype 1 1)
    - [Barnstorming], 3 fold (6 pp) [134-136] (Othertype 1 2)
    - [Rejected], 2 (4 pp) [137-138] (Othertype 1 3)
    - [Abe's philosophy], 1 (2 pp.) [139] (Othertype 2 1)
    - [Newspaper items], 1 (3 pp.) [140] (Othertype 2 2)
    - [In transit], 1 (2 pp) [141] (Othertype 3 1)
    - [Haine's dribble], 1 (3 pp) [142] (Othertype 3 2)
    - [Sylvia], 1 (3 pp) [143] (Othertype 4 1)
    - [Abe's Dream], 1 (3 pp) [144] (Othertype 4 2)
    - [Defeat montage], 1 (3 pp) [145] (Othertype 4 3)
    - [Comedy], 1 (3 pp) [146] (Othertype 5 1)
    - [Romance], 2 (6 pp) [147-148] (Othertype 7 1)
    - [Willouby], 1 (4 pp) [149] (Othertype 8 1)
    - [Tournament], 1 (2 pp) [150] (Othertype 8 2)
    - [Madison Sq trailing] Improvisation for 4 min 15 sec. [instructions], 1 [151] (Othertype 8 3)
    - [Madison Square final], 2 (5 pp) [153-153] (Othertype 9 1)
    - End title, 1 (2 pp) [154] (Othertype 9 2)
- Hard Contract [20th Century-Fox, 1969]
  - North, Alex. (91 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Cunningham, 6 [1-6] (Othertype 1 2)
    - Sheila, 3 [7-9] (Othertype 2 2)
    - Bedroom, 1 [10] (Othertype 2 3, Othertype 3 1)
    - Fullfillment, 10 [11-20] (Othertype 2 3, Othertype 3 1)
    - #1 Man, 12 [21-32] (Othertype 4 2)
    - How to Kiss, 3 [33-35] (Othertype 5 2)
    - All about God, 9[36-44] (Othertype 5 4)
    - Gone, 1 [45] (Othertype 6 1)
    - #2 Man, 7 [46-52] (Othertype 6 2)
    - One woman, 5 [53-57] (Othertype 6 3)
    - Skin, 11 [58-68] (Othertype 6 4, Othertype 7 1)
    - Rape, 3 [69-71] (Othertype 7 4)
    - Hands, 9 [72-80] (Othertype 8 5)
    - Him too, 1 [81] (Othertype 11 2)
    - #3 Man, 1o [82-91] (Othertype 11 3)
    - unspecified (Othertype 12 A)
- Hot Spell [Paramount, 1958]
  - North, Alex. (80 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Main title, 3 [1-3] (Othertype 1 1A)
    - Happy birthday, 2 [4-5] (Othertype 2 BB)
    - Designing Women, 8 [6-13] (Othertype 3 AA)
    - The Lonely Woman, 9 [14-22] (Othertype 3 BB)
    - We never close, 4 [23-26] (Othertype 5 BB)
    - The truth hurts, 9 [27-35] (Othertype 5 CC)
    - The awful truth, 3 [36-38] (Othertype 6 CC)
    - The late comer, 2 [39-40] (Othertype 6 DD)
    - Jack leaves, 8 [41-48] (Othertype 7 AA)
    - Alma's story, 7 [49-55] (Othertype 7 BB)
    - Goodbye Jack, 10 [56-65] (Othertype 7 CC-8AA)
    - News about Jack, 3 [66-68] (Othertype 9 BB)
    - Memories fade, 6 [69-74] (Othertype 10 BB)
    - Finale, 1 [75] (Othertype 10 CC)
    - Alt. End Title, 5 [76-80] (Othertype 10 CCA)
- I'll Cry Tomorrow [MGM, 1955]
  - North, Alex. (74 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - I'll cry tomorrow, 2 [1-2] (Othertype ____)
    - I'll cry, 4 [3-6] (Othertype ____)
    - Don't cry, 2 [7-8] (Othertype 1 2)
    - Bye, L'ams, 2 [9-10] (Othertype 2 1)
    - David, 1 [11] (Othertype 2 6)
    - How soon, 3 [12-14] (Othertype 3 1)
    - Help!, 2 [15-16] (Othertype 3 2)
    - Trance, 2 [17-18] (Othertype 4 7)
    - A Mama's Plea, 4 [19-22] (Othertype 4 8)
    - Confused, 3 [23-25] (Othertype 5 1A, Othertype 5 1B)
    - Pour me!, 2 [26-27] (Othertype 5 1C)
    - Transition, 1 [28] (Othertype 6 1A)
    - Also, 1 [29] (Othertype 6 1B)
    - Tony, 2 [30-31] (Othertype 7 1)
    - Stood up, 3 [32-34] (Othertype 7 2A)
    - Shattered, 2 [35-36] (Othertype 7 2B)
    - Tortured, 2 [37-38] (Othertype 7 2C)
    - Desperate, 3 [39-41] (Othertype 8 5A)
    - A real Heel, 5 [42-46] (Othertype 9 3)
    - Down girl!, 2 [47-48] (Othertype 9 4)
    - Ashamed, 4 [49-52] (Othertype 10 1A)
    - Home sweey, 2 [53-54] (Othertype 10 1B)
    - This is it!, 2 [55-56] (Othertype 10 2)
    - Hold it, 2 [57-58] (Othertype 11 1)
    - The light, 2 [59-60] (Othertype 11 2)
    - Fight to live, 4 [61-64] (Othertype 11 3)
    - Serenity, 4 [65-67] (Othertype 12 1)
    - Burt, 2 [68-69] (Othertype 13 1)
    - End, 2 [70-71] (Othertype 13 3)
    - End title & cast, 3 [72-74] (Othertype 13 3)
- The King & Four Queens [United Artists, 1956]
  - North, Alex. (105 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Prologue, 2 [1-2] (Othertype 1 A)
    - Main title, 12 [3-14] (Othertype 1 1)
    - Rosebud, 3 [15-17] (Othertype 1 1A)
    - Wagon Mound, 9 [18-26] (Othertype 1 2, Othertype 2 1)
    - Ma's Girls, 11 [27-37] (Othertype 2 2)
    - Waiting, 2 [38-39] (Othertype 2 3)
    - Once over, 4 [40-43] (Othertype 3 1)
    - Sabina, 49 44-47] (Othertype 4 1)
    - Sabina, cont'd, 2 [48-49] (Othertype 4 1A)
    - Dan the man!, 1 [50] (Othertype 4 2)
    - Obliged, 1 [51] (Othertype 5 1)
    - Four good reasons, 1 [52] (Othertype 5 2)
    - God's Law, 4 [53-56] (Othertype 5 5, Othertype 6 1)
    - Ruby, 5 [57-61] (Othertype 6 2A)
    - Search, 3 [62-64] (Othertype 6 3)
    - Birdie's dance, 5 [65-69] (Othertype 7 2)
    - Square dance, 9 [70-78] (Othertype 7 3)
    - Oralie, 5 [79-83] (Othertype 7 4)
    - Ruby spurned, 4 [84-87] (Othertype 8 1)
    - Oralie spurned, 2 [88-89] (Othertype 8 2)
    - Spied, 2 [90-91] (Othertype 8 3)
    - Farewell, 3 [92-94] (Othertype 8 4)
    - Gone, 2 [95-96] (Othertype 9 1)
    - The Big Queen and end title, 7 [97-103] (Othertype 9 2)
    - Alternate Ending, 2 [104-105] (Othertype 9 2A)
- The Long Hot Summer [20th Century-Fox, 1958]
  - North, Alex. [Photocopy of holograph musical score (67 leaves)] [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] and some ozalid copies of sections of the score. (Box 6, Folder 22-23)
    - Eula-Rhythm & Blues Style, 12 [1-12] [2 copies]. (Othertype 2 1)
    - Eula-Rhythm & Blues Style [ozalid masters] [ditto. ozalid copies]., 6 [1-6] (Othertype 2 1)
    - Eula, 3 [1-3] (Othertype 2 1)
    - Summertime, 3 [4-6] (Othertype 2 2 3 1)
    - Respect, 3 [7-9] (Othertype 3 2)
    - Gentlemen, 4 [10-13] (Othertype 4 2)
    - Encounter, 5 [14-18] (Othertype 6 1 6 2)
    - Jody, 3 [19-21] (Othertype 6 3)
    - Come on, honey, 3 [22-24] (Othertype 7 1)
    - Barn-burner, 9 [25-33] (Othertype 7 2 8 1)
    - Papa, 3 [34-36] (Othertype 8 1 9 1)
    - Crushed, 1 [37] (Othertype 9 1A)
    - Little Girl, 2 [38-39] (Othertype 9 2)
    - Ashamed, 8 [40-47] (Othertype 9 5 10 1)
    - Loot, 6 [48-53] (Othertype 10 1A)
    - Daddy, 2 [54-55] (Othertype 11 1A)
    - The barn burns, 12 [56-67] (Othertype 11 1 12 1)
- The Last Butterfly
  - North, Alex. Manuscript score. Misc. scores and parts associated with The last butterfly. (Box 57, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Manuscripts and parts. Misc. scores and parts associated with The last butterfly. (Box 58, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Manuscripts and parts. Misc. scores and parts associated with The last butterfly. (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
- Man with the Gun [United Artists, 1955]
  - North, Alex. (98 leaves) [Ozalid copy of holograph musical score] (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Main Title, 3 [1-3] (Othertype 1 1)
    - Main Title-alternate, 7 [4-10] (Othertype 1 1A)
    - Nellie, 3 [11-13] (Othertype 1 3)
    - Encounter, 1 [14] (Othertype 1 4 2 1)
    - Jeff, 2 [15-16] (Othertype 2 2)
    - Query, 6 [17-22] (Othertype 2 3)
    - Goodnite darling, 2 [23-24] (Othertype 2 4)
    - Killings, 1 [25] (Othertype 3 A)
    - Oath, 1 [26] (Othertype 3 1A)
    - Hired, 6 [27-32] (Othertype 3 1)
    - Troubled peacemaker, 2 [33-34] (Othertype 3 2)
    - Bridge, 1 [35] (Othertype 4 A)
    - Gray rider, 2 [36-37] (Othertype 4 1)
    - Action, 2 [38-39] (Othertype 4 2)
    - Warning, 2 [40-41] (Othertype 4 3)
    - Get out of town, 2 [42-43] (Othertype 4 4)
    - Shindig, 7 [44-50] (Othertype 5 1)
    - The Town Tamer, 9 [51-59] (Othertype 5 2)
    - Curfew, 4 [60-63] (Othertype 5 3)
    - Trespass, 2 [64-65] (Othertype 6 1)
    - Exchange, 2 [66-67] (Othertype 6 2)
    - Waiting, 2 [68-69] (Othertype 6 3)
    - Brass, 4 [70-73] (Othertype 6 4 7 1)
    - [Girls dance..], 4 [74-77] (Othertype 7 1A)
    - Town Tamer, 16 [78-93] (Othertype 7 2)
    - Ruse, 1 [94] (Othertype 9 1A)
    - Dade, 1 [95] (Othertype 9 2)
    - Finale, 3 [96-98] (Othertype 9 3)
- A Member of the Wedding [20th Century-Fox, 1953]
  - North, Alex. (61 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Main title, 4 [1-4] (Othertype 1 A)
    - Puzzled, 4 [5-8] (Othertype 1 D)
    - Not elected, 1 [9] (Othertype 2 A)
    - ..And Jasmine, 2 [10-11] (Othertype 2 B)
    - Get Clean, 2 [12-13] (Othertype 2 C)
    - Frankie Sobs, 3 [14-16] (Othertype 3 A)
    - Leaving town, 2 [17-18] (Othertype 3 B)
    - Lonely Frankie, 14 [19-32] (Othertype 4 A-E)
    - [Fade under Good Morning Papa..], 1 [33] (Othertype ______)
    - Wedding gown, 1 [34] (Othertype 5 A)
    - Bernie's Philosophy, 5 [35-39] (Othertype 6 B)
    - Be reasonable, 6 [40-45] (Othertype 8 D)
    - Meet Life, 2 [46-47] (Othertype 9 C)
    - Meet Reality, 4 [48-51] (Othertype 9 F)
    - Meet Death, 3 [52-54] (Othertype 9 G)
    - More Mature, 6 [55-60] (Othertype 10 A)
    - End Title, 1 [61] (Othertype 10 B)
- Les Miserables [20th Century-Fox, 1952]
  - North, Alex. (83 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Main title, 2 [1-2] (Othertype ______)
    - Sea, 1 [3] (Othertype 1 3)
    - Valjean's Release, 6 [4-9] (Othertype 2 1)
    - Despair, 3 [10-12] (Othertype 2 2)
    - Benevolence, 2 [13-14] (Othertype 3 1)
    - Supplications, 1 [15] (Othertype 3 2)
    - Admonition, 2 [16-17] (Othertype 3 3)
    - Runaway, 3 [18-20] (Othertype 3 4)
    - The Town, 3 [21-23] (Othertype 4 1)
    - First Phase, 1 [24] (Othertype 4 2)
    - [no title], 2 [25-26] (Othertype 4 4, Othertype 5 1)
    - Javert, 4 [27-30] (Othertype 4 4, Othertype 5 1 (new))
    - Fantine, 7 [31-36] (Othertype 5 3)
    - Retribution, 3 [37-39] (Othertype 6 1, Othertype 7 1-2)
    - Robert, 2 [40-41] (Othertype 7 2)
    - Robert, 1 [42] (Othertype 7 2A)
    - Cosette, 2 [43-44] (Othertype 8 1)
    - Marius, 6 [45-50] (Othertype 8 2)
    - Decisions, 2 [51-52] (Othertype 9 A)
    - Revolution, 1 [53] (Othertype 9 1)
    - [no title], 21 [54-74] (Othertype 9 X, Othertype 10 1)
    - Chase, 5 [75-79] (Othertype 10 11)
    - Denoument, 4[80-83] (Othertype 11 2)
- The Misfits [United Artists, 1961]
  - North, Alex. (69 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Main title, 6 [1-6] (Othertype 1 1)
    - New Life, 2 [7-8] (Othertype 2 1)
    - Roslyn, 3 [9-11] (Othertype 3 3, Othertype 4 1)
    - Love's Reverie, 8 [12-19] (Othertype 4 2, Othertype 4 3)
    - Love Idyll #2, 3 [20-22] (Othertype 4 4)
    - Compassion, 3 [23-25] (Othertype 8 2)
    - Compassion for Guido, 3 [26-28] (Othertype 8 3)
    - Help, 7 [29-35] (Othertype 9 1)
    - Disagreement, 6 [36-41] (Othertype 10 1)
    - Roundup, 11 [42-52] (Othertype 10 2)
    - [no title], 5 [53-57] (Othertype 12 1)
    - Trying for freedom, 6 [58-63] (Othertype 12 2)
    - Resolved-end title, 6 [64-69] (Othertype 13 2)
- The Outrage [MGM, 1964]
  - North, Alex. [Handwritten in pencil, notes, (8 leaves)] [Cue sheet, (2 leaves)]. [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score (36 leaves)] (Box 7, Folder 28-29)
    - Carasco, 12 [1-12] (Box-folder 7/29, Othertype 3 1)
    - The Wife, 2 [13-14] (Othertype 3 2)
    - Struggle, 6 [15-20] (Othertype 4 1)
    - Deeper, 1 [21] (Othertype 6 2)
    - And Deeper, 2 [22-23] (Othertype 6 2A)
    - Husband, 9 [24-32] (Othertype 7 1)
    - Con Man, 2 [33-34] (Othertype 10 1)
    - End Credits, 2 [35-36] (Othertype 10 2)
- Passover Plot
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 69, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 70, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 71, Folder unknown container)
- Penitente
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 24, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 25, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Manuscripts and parts. (Box 65, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Manuscripts and parts. (Box 66, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Manuscripts and Parts. (Box 67, Folder unknown container)
- Pony Soldier [20th Century-Fox, 1952]
  - North, Alex. (106 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Main title, 5 [1-5] (Othertype ______)
    - [no title-end of Kanah's scream], 3 [6-8] (Othertype 1 3)
    - [no title-diss.-Indian drums], 8 [9-16] (Othertype 1 5)
    - [no title - Konahs party], 6 [17-22] (Othertype 1 6, Othertype 2 A)
    - [no title-flaming arrows], 4 [23-26] (Othertype 2 1)
    - Mirage, 8 [27-34] (Othertype 3 1)
    - [no title-diss-Indian camp], 4 [35-38] (Othertype 3 2)
    - Standing Bear, 5 [39-44] (Othertype 3 3, Othertype 4 1)
    - [no title - Start-drums recorded], 2 [45-46] (Othertype 4 1A)
    - [no title-McDonald watches], 3 [47-49] (Othertype 4 2)
    - [no title-cut-c.u.-Indian Boy]., 6 [50-55] (Othertype 5 1A)
    - [no title], 5 [56-60] (Othertype 5 3, Othertype 6 1)
    - [no title], 7 [61-66] (Othertype 6 2)
    - Jess, 16 [67-82] (Othertype 7 1)
    - [no title], 11 [83-93] (Othertype 8 1)
    - [no title-cut to Firr Pile], 6 [94-99] (Othertype 8 9, Othertype 9 1)
    - [no title-Mac looks down], 3 [100-102] (Box 9 2)
    - [no title-Maestro], 4 [103-106] (Box 9 4)
- Prizzi's Honor
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 37, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 38, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 39, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 40, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 72, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 73, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 74, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 75, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 76, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 77, Folder unknown container)
- The Racers [20th Century-Fox, 1955]
  - North, Alex. (68 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score, unless otherwise noted] (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - [no title - full], 3 [1-3] (Othertype 1 1)
    - Monte Carlo, 3 [4-6] (Othertype 1 2)
    - [no title-no orch. seen], 3 [7-9] (Othertype 1 3)
    - Much too close, 4 [10-13] (Othertype 2 1)
    - Roulette, 8 [14-22] (Othertype 2 2)
    - Stars or nothing, 3 [23-25] (Othertype 3 1A)
    - [no title-diss-cow in field], 3 [26-28] (Othertype 4 1)
    - (Band) German, 4 [29-32] (Othertype 4 3)
    - Decision, 10 [33-42] (33-40 ozalid copies) (Othertype 6 1)
    - Truth, 2 [43-44] (Othertype 7 1)
    - [no title-grand racer..], 9 [45-53] (51-53=ozalid copies) (Othertype 8 1)
    - New, 12 [54-65] (Othertype 12 1A)
    - End Title, 3 [66-68] (Othertype 13 1)
- The Rainmaker [Paramount, 1956]
  - North, Alex. (128 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Par. Seal, 2 [1-2] (Othertype 1 AA)
    - Prologue, 4 [3-6] (Othertype 1 BB)
    - Main title, 5 [7-11] (Othertype 1 CC)
    - The Curry Ranch, 2 [12-13] (Othertype 2 BB)
    - Little Pete Pt. I, 1 [14] (Othertype 2 CC)
    - Little Pete Pt. II, 2 [15-16] (Othertype 3 AA)
    - Dry Lake, 3 [17-19] (Othertype 3 BB)
    - Pride, 3 [20-22] (Othertype 3 CC)
    - Big Feet, 3 [23-25] (Othertype 3 DD, Othertype 4 AA)
    - File's not coming, 3 [26-28] (Othertype 4 BB)
    - Enter the rainmaker, 1 [29] (Othertype 5 BB)
    - The deal is set, 1 [30] (Othertype 6 BB)
    - Wet Socks, 5 [31-35] (ozalid copy of conductors score) (Othertype 6 B1X)
    - Starbuck's Story Pt. I, 3 [36-38] (Othertype 6 CC)
    - Starbuck's Story Pt. II, 9 [39-47] (Othertype 7 AA)
    - Noah at Bay, 4 [48-51] (ozalid copy) (Othertype 8 AX)
    - The Vamp, 5 [52-56] (Othertype 8 BB)
    - The Gentlemen Caller, Pt I, 8 [57-64] (ozalid copy) (Othertype 8 DX)
    - The Gentlemen Caller Pt. I, 6 [65-70] (Othertype 8 DDX)
    - The Gentelemen Caller Pt. II, 1 [71] (Othertype 9 A)
    - Flibbartigibbet, 8 [72-79] (Othertype 9 BB)
    - The Tack Room, 6 [80-85] (Othertype 9 CC, Othertype 10 AA)
    - No Dream, 3 [86-88] (ozalid copy) (Othertype 10 B1X)
    - Golden Fleece, 6 [89-94] (Othertype 10 BB)
    - I'm Pretty Pt. I, 5 [95-99] (Othertype 10 CC)
    - I'm Pretty Pt. II, 4 [100-103] (Othertype 11 AA)
    - Young Lovers, 2 [104-105] (Othertype 11 BB)
    - Starbucks Confession, 11 [106-116] (Othertype 12 AA)
    - Starbucks Confession, Pt. II, 4 [117-120] (Othertype 12 AA1)
    - A change of heart, 1 [121] (Othertype 12 CC)
    - A change of heart Pt. II, 7 [122-128] (Othertype 13 AA)
- The Rose Tattoo [Paramount, 1955]
  - North, Alex. (103 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Main title, 5 [1-5] (Othertype ____)
    - Hello, 4 [6-9] (Othertype 1 BB)
    - Night run, 4 [10-13] (Othertype I C, Othertype 2 A)
    - Premonition, 4 [14-17] (Othertype 2 BB)
    - Bereavement, 2 18-19] (Othertype 2 DD)
    - [no title], 2 [20-21] (Othertype 2 EE2)
    - Come Le Rose, 1 [22] (Othertype 2 E1P)
    - Tmorrow's Kiss, 1 [23] (Othertype 2 FF)
    - Late Civics, 2 [24-25] (Othertype 3 AA)
    - Graduation, 6 [26-31] (Othertype 3 BB)
    - Clowns, 6 [32-37] (Othertype 3 D, Othertype 4 A)
    - Bacio, 1 [38] (Othertype 4 C)
    - Bacio, 3 [39-41] (Othertype 4 D)
    - Introduction, 3 [42-44] (Othertype 5 A)
    - A Pledge of Honor, 6 [45-50] (Othertype 5 B, Othertype 6 A)
    - Church-Marry a Rose, 1 [51] (Othertype 6 B1)
    - A shocking Resemblance, 3 [52-54] (Othertype 7 B)
    - Il Matadore, 8 [55-62] (Othertype 8 B)
    - Late Date #1, 4 [63-66] (Othertype 9 A)
    - Big Moment, 2 [67-68] (Othertype 9 D)
    - Rose II, 5 [69-73] (Othertype 10 C)
    - Shattered Love, 3 [74-76] (Othertype 10 E)
    - Late Date #2, 3 [77-79] (Othertype 11 A)
    - Backyard Disturbance, 2 [80-81] (Othertype 11 B)
    - Drunken Clown, 5 [82-86] (Othertype 11 C)
    - Young Love, 6 [87-92] (Othertype 11 D)
    - A Rude Awakening, 2 [93-94] (Othertype 12 A)
    - Mama's Blessing, 7 [95-101] (Othertype 12 B)
    - Finale, 2 [102-103] (Othertype 12 D)
- Sanctuary [20th Century-Fox, 1961]
  - North, Alex. (77 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Main Title, 4 [1-4] (Othertype ____)
    - I remember, 5 [5-9] (Othertype 1 3, Othertype 2 1)
    - Candyman [typewritten musical breakdown], 4 [10-13] (Othertype ____)
    - Candyman, 6 [14-19] (Othertype 4 1, Othertype 5 1)
    - Sanctuary [typewritten music breakdown], 9 [20-28] (Othertype ____)
    - Sleep little lush [typewritten music breakdown], 2 [29-30] (Othertype ____)
    - Sleep little lush, 6 [31-36] (Othertype 5 5)
    - You're mine, 4 [37-40] (Othertype 6 2, Othertype 6 3)
    - Narration #1, 2 [41-42] (Othertype 6 5)
    - Narration #2, 3 [43-45] (Othertype 7 1)
    - Narration #3, 3 [46-48] (Othertype 7 1A)
    - Romance, 6 [49-54] (Othertype 7 2)
    - Revelation [typewritten music breakdown], 2 [55-56] (Othertype ____)
    - Revelation, 2 [57-58] (Othertype 7 3, Othertype 8 1)
    - Should I, 4 [59-62] (Othertype 8 2)
    - Candy's Return, 5 [63-67] (Othertype 8 3)
    - Little Girl, 6 [68-73] (Othertype 8 4)
    - Believe, 4 [74-77] (Othertype 10 1)
- The Scoundrel
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 60, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 61, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 61, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 62, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 63, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 64, Folder unknown container)
- Shanks
  - North, Alex. Manuscripts and parts. (Box 49, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Manuscripts and parts. (Box 50, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Manuscripts and parts. (Box 51, Folder unknown container)
- Shoes of the Fisherman [MGM, 1968]
  - North, Alex. (123 leaves) [Holograph, in pencil, of musical score] (Box 9, Folder 35-36)
    - Overture Part I and II, 6 [1-6] (Box-folder 9/36, Othertype ____)
    - Overture III, 8 [7-14] (Othertype ____)
    - Main title, 6 [15-20] (Othertype 1 1)
    - Kiril's Release, 3 [21-23] (Othertype 1 2)
    - Kamenen, 1 [24] (Othertype 2 1)
    - Roman Band, 2 [25-26] (Othertype 3 1A)
    - Pope and Kiril, 2 [27-28] (Othertype 3 2, Othertype 4 1)
    - Party, 1 [29] (Othertype 4 2)
    - Announcement, 1 [30] (Othertype 5 2)
    - St. Peter's Square, 1 [31] (Othertype 5 3)
    - Ceremony, 6 [32-37] (Othertype 6 1)
    - Cardinal's Arrival, 5 [38-42] (Othertype 7 1)
    - Election of Pope, 18 [41-58] (Othertype 8 1)
    - Kiril's Past, 2 [59-60] (Othertype 8 2)
    - Kiril proclaimed Pope, 7 [61-66] (Othertype 9 1)
    - White Smoke, 1 [67] (Othertype 10 1)
    - Crowds approval, 2 [68-69] (Othertype 10 2)
    - Leone, 2 [70-71] (Othertype 11 1)
    - Zoo, 5 [72-76] (Othertype 12 1)
    - Kiril's Loneliness, 3 [77-79] (Othertype 12 2)
    - Adventure, 2 [80-81] (Othertype 12 3)
    - Consolation, 13 [82-94] (Othertype 13 1)
    - Romantic, 2 [95-96] (Othertype 14 1)
    - Commissions Reaction, 1 [102] (Othertype 15 1)
    - Tel Death, 4 [103-106] (Othertype 16 1, Othertype 17 1)
    - Solitary Pilgrimage, 3 [107-109] (Othertype 17 2)
    - Gathering, 4 [110-113] (Othertype 18 2)
    - Coronation, 7 [114-120] (Othertype 18 3)
    - End Title, 3 [121-123] (Othertype 19 1)
- Silent Night
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 52, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 53, Folder unknown container)
  - North, Alex. Parts. (Box 54, Folder unknown container)
- Somebody killed her husband
  - North, Alex. Main title. Score and parts. Reel 1 - part 1. Copy of score, onion skins [4 leaves] and parts. Flts - 3, oboes - 1, clars - 2, bsn - 1, hns - 3, trpts - 2, trbs - 2, tuba -1, perc - 3, pno - 3, vlns- 4, vlas - 1, cello & bass - 2. (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - North, Alex. Jerry. Score and parts. Reel 1 - part 2. Copy of score, onion skins [18 leaves] and parts. Flts - 3, oboe - 1, clar - 2, vlns - 4, vlas - 1, cello - 1, bass - 1, fender bass - 1, perc - 7, pno - 6, harp - 1, guitar - 1. (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - North, Alex. Jenny's entrance. Score and parts. Reel 1 - part 3. Copy of score, onion skins [1 leave] and parts. Vlns - 4, vla - 1, cello - 1, bass - 1, perc - 1, pno - 3, harp - 1. (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - North, Alex. Joyful Jerry. Score and parts. Reel 1 - part 4. Copy of score, onion skins [4 leaves], and parts. Flts - 3, oboe - 1, clar - 1, bass clar - 1, hns - 3, trpts - 2, trbs - 2, perc - 3, pno - 3, harp, - 1, vlns - 4, vla - 1, cello - 1, bass - 1, fender bass - 1. (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - North, Alex. Music box. Score and parts. Reel 1 - part 4A. Copy of score, onion skins [2 leaves] and parts. perc - 7. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - North, Alex. Session sheet "A" orch. list of cues, timings, 3/15/78, 3/16/78. (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - North, Alex. Session sheet "C" Orch. list of cues, timings, 3/17/78. (Box 78, Folder 7)